pbisrewards.com 2018-08-15

# PBIS Rewards Website Privacy Policy | PBIS Rewards

## Overview

Welcome to [https://www.pbisrewards.com](https://www.pbisrewards.com/) (“Website”), the website and online service of PBIS Rewards (“we”, “our” or “us”). PBIS Rewards is a service of Motivating Systems, LLC dba PBIS Rewards. The **PBIS Rewards Website Privacy Policy** covers the use of this Website, a website that informs and educates visitors to the Website about the Platform Service also known as PBIS Rewards. Our Website Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use and disclose personal information of users and visitors to the PBIS Rewards website.

This Website Privacy Policy does NOT cover the use of the PBIS Rewards Platform service. The [PBIS Rewards Platform Terms of Service](https://www.pbisrewards.com/policies/platform-terms-of-service/) covers privacy issues, including student data privacy, as part of its comprehensive set of protections for subscribers and users of the service.

## What Personal Data We Collect and Why We Collect It

If you choose to use our Website ([https://www.pbisrewards.com](https://www.pbisrewards.com/)), then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation with this Privacy Policy. The Personal Information that we collect is used for the following purposes.

  * To understand how visitors use our Website so that we can improve the experience of visitors.
  * To market our services to visitors who we believe can benefit from our PBIS Rewards service.
  * To provide resources and information to the users who make requests for resources and information.

We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

### Form Data

Some of the data we collect is information you give directly to us by filling out a form on our Website. Some of the forms are request forms that you fill out requesting that we send you more information about our service or a specific resource. Some of the forms are requests for support. These forms will ask you for your name, email address, and telephone number in addition to other information required to fulfill your request.

### Log Data

Whenever you visit our Website, we collect information that your browser sends to us as Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser version, pages of our Website that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, and other statistics. We use this data to understand how visitors use our Website, to look for unauthorized uses of our Website, and to troubleshoot problems with the performance of our Website. These log files are generally deleted after 30 days.

### Email Subscriptions

We will also ask you if you would like us to add your email to one of our email lists. If you answer “yes” to this question or directly subscribe to our newsletter through the newsletter subscription form, then we will save your data so that we can send email communications to you about promotions and offers for our service and other information that we believe will help you make your school or organization a better place. We do use third-parties to help us communicate with you, but we do not rent, sell, or share your email address with third-parties who will market their own services to you.

### Cookies

Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored in a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer or mobile device. It may contain certain data, including, but not limited to: the name of the server that has placed it there, an identifier in the form of a unique number, and an expiration date (if applicable to the cookie). Cookies are managed by the web browser on your computer (i.e. Internet Explorer, Firefox, Google Chrome, or Safari). Our Website uses these cookies to collect information and to improve our Website. You can block cookies from our Website, but it may make some features of the Website unusable.

Some of the cookies are put in place so that we can market our services to you using third-party advertising services and some of the cookies are put in place so that we can collect anonymous demographic data about visitors to our Website so that we can better tailor content to our audience.

### Pixel Tracking

In addition to using Cookies, our Website may employ “pixel tracking”, a common process which may be used in connection with our advertisements on other sites. Pixel tracking involves the use of pixel tags that are not visible to the user and consist of a few lines of computer code. Pixel tracking measures the effectiveness of advertisements and compiles aggregate and specific usage statistics. A “pixel tag” is an invisible tag placed on certain pages of websites that is used to track an individual user’s activity. We may access these pixel tags to identify activity and interests that may allow us to better match our services and other offers with your interests and needs. For example, if you visit our Website from an advertisement we placed on another website, the pixel tag will let us know which website and advertisement led you to visit our Website. If you visit our Website, and we link you to another website, we may also be able to determine that you were sent to and/or transacted with a third-party website. This data is collected for use in our marketing and research.

### Analytics

We use Google Analytics to help us understand the use of our Website. This service collects information sent by your browser as part of a web page request. This information may include cookies, your IP address, and data from sites that partner with Google, and their use of it is governed by their privacy policy. For more information on Google Analytics cookies, visit [www.google.com/policies](https://www.google.com/policies). To opt-out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites visit [http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). This will allow you to download and install a Google Analytics cookie-free web browser.

### Live Chat

We use a third party, live chat service on our Website to provide a convenient means of communication for visitors on our website. The information that you provide to a PBIS Rewards team member during the live chat is stored in chat logs by the third party service provider and may you used by PBIS Rewards to provide additional information required to fulfill your request.

If a visitor self-identifies themselves as a Student during the live chat session we will:

  * Direct the Student to communicate with their school for questions and information regarding PBIS and PBIS Rewards.
  * Not confirm school record, use, or student data.
  * Promptly delete their live chat logs.

### Embedded Content From Other Websites

Pages on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, tweets etc.). This embedded content from other websites will behave in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website directly.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account with and are logged in to that website.

### Service Providers

We employ third-party companies due to the following reasons:

  * To assist us in marketing related tasks and communication.
  * To assist us in analyzing how our Website is used.

We do share our Website users personal information with these third parties so that they can act on our behalf in communicating to you and to help us perform better. They are obligated to protect your personal information and not use it for any other purpose other than assisting us as we serve you.

### Links to Other Sites

Our Website may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by us. Therefore, we strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.

### Children under the Age of 13

We do not market our services to children of any age and this includes children under the age of 13. We do not produce marketing content that is targeted at children of any age, including children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect any Personally Identifiable Information from children through our Website under any circumstances.

If a user self-identifies themselves as a Student through any contact form on this Website, we take the following actions:

  * We will not send an email confirmation to that user’s email address.
  * We will not allow that user’s email address to subscribe to our email lists.
  * We immediately delete the form entry from our records.

If you become aware of a child giving us information through this Website, please contact us at the address below so that we can remove that information.

## Contact Information

#### Physical address

PBIS Rewards  
223 NW 2nd St. STE 300  
Evansville, IN 47708

#### By phone

812-434-6685

#### By email

## Policy Revisions

We may update this Privacy Policy whenever new developments in law, regulations, or technology make it necessary, and we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. We encourage you to visit this Privacy Policy page frequently so that you are familiar with our commitment to your privacy.

This policy was last modified on Aug 14, 2018.
